archinect.com 2019-04-02

# Privacy Policy | Archinect

**The privacy of our visitors to Archinect is important to us.**

At Archinect, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Archinect, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

We only process your Personal Data in accordance with applicable data protection and privacy laws. For the purposes of UK and EU data protection legislation, the data controller is Extra Medium , Inc. (DBA Archinect) of 2785 E Foothill Blvd, Suite 110, Pasadena, CA 91107 USA. Archinect's Data Protection Officer is Paul Petrunia. He may be contacted at privacy@archinect.com.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Chrome, Safari or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This includes the ability to login to some of our features, such as the discussion forums.

We also use third party advertisements on Archinect to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real job ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as interior design ads to someone who frequents interior design sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
